# NGUYỄN VIỆT HÙNG

# BACK-FND DEVELOPER



0395746139



hnv2311@gmail.com 🦞 Ho Chi Minh City





**2**3/11/2001



portfolio.hocduthu.com

## PROFILE INFO

Back-end developer with 1.5 years of experience developing web and web API applications using .NET Core, SQL Server, MySQL. Understanding OOP principles, software development methodologies, git version control, and agile practices. Self-motivated, proactive, and capable of working independently as well as in a team environment, and also ability to analyze and design databases

## **EXPERIENCE**

Dec 2023 - May 2024

P&B Food Viet Nam I Thu Dau Mot City, Binh Duong Province

#### Freelancer Fulltime

- Database and Backend: Design database and build backend using .NET 8 and clean architecture principles
- Auth Module: Implement ASP.NET Identity and JWT with authentication and authorization features, including refresh token functionality
- Payment Integration Module: Develop functions for PayOs and Momo payment gateway transactions via API
- Background Job Module: Use Hangfire for scheduled tasks (e.g., daily order summaries, email sending)
- Deployment: Utilize GitHub Actions to trigger and process code builds into Docker images
- Mobile App: Develop a full Flutter mobile application using an existing template

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

FPT Software | District 9, Ho Chi Minh City

## .Net Intern

- Analyze existing application code, write unit tests, and debug the application
- · Build and deploy the system to Azure cloud

#### **PROJECTS**

**PerfectBreakfast WebApp** (.NET 8, React, MySql, Cache, Docker...) Food ordering system and manages stakeholders into a unified process

**TsdDelivery WebApp** (.NET 7, React, Sql Server, Cache, Azure...) A system that allows customers and drivers to book and receive orders for goods transportation

All Projects: <a href="https://portfolio.hocduthu.com/project">https://portfolio.hocduthu.com/project</a>

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2024 | FPT University

**Software Engineering | Graduated** 

Degree Classification: Good

#### **SKILLS**

Programming languages:

• C#, Java, Dart, JavaScript

# Framework:

• .Net, basic Flutter

# Database:

• SQL (SQL Server), MySQL

# Cloud:

• Basic Azure, AWS, VPS

#### Others:

- GitHub, Redis, Unit Test (Xunit)
- · Linux OS, Docker
- English

# **ACTIVITIES**

Write and share effective articles on technology and engineering on my blog Hoc Đủ Thứ

## CERTIFICATE

**Linux Fundamentals** 

**Computer Communications** 

0

Google Project Management

0 0

Software Development Lifecycle

0